Berkin Kınay

Front-End Developer

berkinkinay.dev

İzmir, Turkey

GitHub: github.com/berkinkinay Linkedin: linkedin.com/berkin-kinay

Phone: +(90) 0532 173 92 88 Email: helloberkin@gmail.com



Known Programming Languages and Tools

JavaScript, TypeScript

HTML5, CSS3,

Node.js, Three.js,

React.js, Vue.js, Preact,

ESlint, Vite, Jest

Redux,

Git, Postman,

Vercel, Netlify,

Element UI, Sass

TailwindCSS, Bootstrap,

Styled-Components

Figma, Adobe Ai, Adobe Ps.

Work Experience

Software Designer // 2020-08 – 2021-09
Internship Development Team

5 | ID | //2024 C

Frontend Developer // 2021 – Current -

About me

My name is Berkin Kınay. I'm a Front-End Developer with a couple of experience in last two years. My education process started in 2020 and I really love Computer Science since day I started.

Introducing Myself About Software Development

My field of Interest's are building new Web Technologies and Products and also in areas related to Deep Learning and Natural Languages Processing. Whenever possible, I also apply my passion for developing products with NodeJS and Modern JavaScript Library and Frameworks like React.js, Vue.js and Next.js etc.

I can optimize your applications and provide high-performance. I work on JavaScript technologies mostly. I'm also coding to create clean build with elegant code for Backend and Server-side development with TypeScript and Node.js

Social skills and My Strongest Areas About Programming

Active listening, teamwork, motivating others, leadership, problem solving, communication, offering help and support to others.

Natural Language Processing, Algorithms, Web Development, CSS Architecture

Education

Necip Demir /// 2013 -- 2017

Usak University /// 2020 -- Current

Computer Programming

I'm currently pursuing my associate degree

Languages known

English Fluent in writing and speaking as well (B2-C1)

-

Turkish Native